I'm the miracle doctor who drowned in your book.
أنا الطبيب الذي غرق في كتابك
Gu Xiaofeng.
قو شياو فنغ
Are you...
هل
You're finally awake.
لقد استيقظت أخيرًا
It's true.
حقاً؟
Yes.
نعم
My brother...
أخي
Cherish the present.
اعتز به الآن
Can you tell me
يمكنك أن تخبرني
What's wrong with you?
ما خطبك؟
Don't ask anything.
لا تسألي أي شيء
I just want to hug you quietly.
أريد فقط أن أعانقك بهدوء
Okay.
حسنا
Gosh.
مزعج
They're giving us sugar.
إنهم يعطينا السكر
Let's show them too.
لنرش لهم أيضًا -حسنًا -
Gu Xiaomei, come to the hospital.
جو تعالي إلى المستشفى
My grandpa...
جدي
Something happened to Grandpa Mo.
خبر سيء حدث شيء لجد مو
Grandpa Mo!
الجد مو
Grandpa.
جدي
Gu Xiaomei is here.
الآنسة قو هنا
Xiaofeng.
شياو فنغ
Coming.
أنا قادم
Xiaofeng is here.
شياو فنغ هنا
How could this happen?
كيف حدث هذا؟
Grandpa Mo, I can save you.
جدي مو يمكن لشياو فنغ إنقاذك
Xiaofeng.
شياو فنغ
Don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا
The hospital will never give up on treating patients.
من المستحيل أن تتخلى المستشفى عن علاج المريض
Feng.
فنغ
Grandpa Mo's illness...
مرض الجد مو
can't be helped even if the deity comes.
حتى لو جاء الخالد
Grandpa Mo.
جدي مو
I'm useless.
شياو فنغ غير فائدة
I can't save you.
لا أستطيع إنقاذك
Xiaofeng.
شياو فنغ
call me Grandpa Mo according to seniority.
تناديني الجد مو وفقًا للأسلف
In terms of medical skills,
من ناحية المهارات الطبية
I should call you master.
يجب أن أناديك بالسيد
Don't blame yourself.
لا تلوم نفسك
Son.
يا حفيدي
Follow me.
اتبعني
Feng studied Chinese medicine.
شياو فنغ تتعلم الطب الصيني
Chinese medicine?
الطب الصيني
has thousands of years of history in our country.
لديه تاريخ دولتنا منذ آلاف السنين
You have to believe it.
يجب أن تثق به
I believe it.
أصدقك
You've recovered.
إذا تعافيت
I promise you I will study medicine.
أعدك أنني سأعلم الطب بجد
Sure.
حسناً
Grandpa.
جدي
Grandpa Mo.
الجد مو
Don't scare me, grandpa.
لا تخيفني يا جدي
Grandpa Mo, wake up.
جدي مو جدي استيقظ
Grandpa Mo!
جدي جدي مو
Grandpa, don't scare me.
جدي لا تخيفني
Grandpa Mo.
جدي مو
I won't make you angry again, grandpa.
لن أغضبك مرة أخرى يا جدي
Wake up!
استيقظ
Wake up, grandpa!
استيقظ يا جدي
My grandpa told me to give this to you.
طلب مني جدي أن أعطيك هذا
Feng.
شياو فنغ
Help the dying.
أنقذ الأرواح والجرح
It's the responsibility of
ورث الثقافة الطبية الصينية
is the responsibility of Chinese medicine.
هو مسؤولية الطبيب الصيني
But my grandson is extremely talented.
لكن موهبتي سيئة للغاية
He's limited.
قدرته محدودة
Please take care of him.
سأعتمد عليه في المستقبل
Ren Yi.
رن يي
Grandpa Mo is very nice.
الجد مو جيد جدا
He taught me everything.
علمني كل ما لديه
He always thinks about me.
ويفكر بي مهما كان لذيذا
But I don't have Grandpa Mo anymore.
لكن لن يكون لدي الجد مو بعد الآن
You still have me.
سأكون معك في المستقبل
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث
let's face it together.
سنواجه معا
OK?
اتفقنا؟
Ren Yi.
رن يي